Feels good to eat outside
for a change, for real!
Everyone needs to take it easy sometimes.
But man, this sucks...
What does?
I thought we were gonna win...
We can't find the Queen's headquarters since
it's hidden away with the Concealment Right.
There's really not a way
for us to win, for real...
Don't worry too much and eat up!
We can still use the public
with the Emperor's announcements.
Yeah... I guess...
You guys sure are down in the dumps!
I get how you feel, really.
Ren Iruga!
Tasuketsu: Fate of the Majority
How did you find us?!
Whoa, easy now.
Remember that envelope
from the Emperor operation?
It came with an antenna
to trace whoever opened it.
With my Tracing Right!
Die
I opened that envelope!
Would you happen to be the current Emperor?
I'm not just here to drop by. I came to
share some valuable information.
Valuable information?
At this rate, there's no way
you can defeat the Queen.
I'm assuming that you've already figured out
that the Queen can obtain Rights
without an owner.
Y-Yeah...
Attack
Attack, defense, revival...
even Rights to conceal herself.
Defense
Revival
Concealment
The Queen has a strong hand
and a full slate...
and that's where my info comes into play!
Today, I'm gonna teach you
the hottest source of information!
Knight Kato...
He's the one you should win over if you
want a safe way to extract information!
Didn't Pres say he planted
something in Knight?
I don't know if I'd blindly believe
the President if I were you.
Not that I'd stop you guys...
it's fun to watch anyway.
Don't blindly believe... Yagihashi?
What's that supposed to mean?
It's Iruga we're dealing with.
We may be better off ignoring him.
Yeah, for real!
Good grief...
I wondered what you meant
when you told me to listen here.
Come to find out, you just wanted to
talk about me behind my back.
I only told the truth!
It's not exactly helpful, though.
I'm fully on board now.
Count me in, too.
Still, I'm surprised you're
willing to do this, Iruga.
Aww, shucks.
I just still believe
in Saneatsu Narita, that's all.
Sorry to tell you guys this, but that
Yagihashi guy reeks of lies to me.
I guess it's weird that he didn't
mention the Queen sooner, but...
He's always been that way, you know.
I'm not telling you to turn
your back on him. But...
It doesn't hurt to be cautious.
Omi, what the hell are you...
Feels awesome!
Whoooooa! I can feel
the tension melting away!
We gotta do this more often!
The Emperor is my deputy officer...
I won't allow any defiance against him.
Is that understood?
I don't get any of this.
Lady Kisaragi was in contact with the Emperor?
I guess.
Even the Emperor follows her lead...
That's the power of Lady Kisaragi.
By the way, where's Kou?
I didn't see him.
Who knows. Don't care either way.
I'm not happy about these newcomers, but...
with them around, Kou
can't get too comfortable.
Can't complain about that.
Looks like there's some
internal conflict in play.
And what's he doing on our side?
Stop. My only focus should be
on serving Lady Kisaragi!
Wait a second!
So you're saying that you killed me
because of a misunderstanding?!
You were about to tell them about our plan.
I thought you were betraying us.
Besides, the whole point of the infiltration
was to defeat both the Queen and the Emperor!
You're right... I shouldn't have
acted on my own judgment.
That's my fault.
Let's go back to square one...
Are you still willing to join us?
Of course.
Good! Then let's start over.
Tell me why you were willing
to reveal our plan in the first place.
Because of Raion Ouno.
The current Emperor's chance at winning
is much higher with him on their side.
I think we should join forces.
That kid...
Okay.
I trust your judgment.
Knight...
Can you still use your Destruction Right?
Perfect.
I was worried my unusual tactic
wouldn't work, but we're good.
Unusual?
Immobilization Right
My Immobilization Right comes
with both physical and principle fixation.
Physical Fixation
Principle Fixation
I used principle fixation to secure ownership
of Rights between Knight, Lili, and myself.
You secured your... ownership?
As long as Knight or Lili is alive,
I maintain ownership of my own Right.
And as long as I own the Immobilization
Right, they both maintain their Rights.
I see...
Someone's coming!
Knight!
Hirayama... Ebina...
You're interrupting our date.
I've already reported you two
to Lady Kisaragi.
But she didn't give any orders.
You understand what that means?
It means you're less
of a nuisance than an eyesore.
You don't even amount
to the threat of a fly.
Go ahead and play make-believe all you want.
If you ever stand in the way,
I'll dispose of you with my eyes closed.
Hey...
Don't get too cocky and underestimate me
just because you're one of the Three Powers.
Oh? Will you prove me wrong?
Whatever.
Don't mind me. I'm just acting up.
They said to look for clues
to the Queen but...
At least you get a chance
to get some fresh air, Souma.
You've been sticking next to Gobo
guarding him this entire time.
Yeah, I guess.
Explosion Right.
Is he the Queen's servant?
Look at me, keeping my cool for a change.
Huh? Queen...? What?
Must be a surviving civilian...
Why did you attack us like that?!
Tell the truth!
T-To survive you have to kill
before you get killed!
Any Rights?!
Wh-Wha? Um, I'm...
Do you have any or not?!
Make up your mind!
Scary...
I have some still sealed in envelopes!
Hand them over!
Hold up, isn't this called... extortion?
Right
There was another one I found, but
it disappeared before I could grab it...
Disappeared?!
It's true! Please believe me!
When did you find it?
Y-Yesterday!
Please! Let me go!
Right
They must have recovered
abandoned envelopes,
which would make these valuable.
Should we take them back with us?
Or should we bring this dude along?
Wait, where did he go?!
He took off.
Why didn't you stop him?!
So that's how everything went down.
Right
I think these are the last of them.
Apparently, envelopes across Tokyo
were recovered yesterday.
Then first thing's first...
It's 23:55 PM.
This is your Emperor speaking.
Another fake message? For real?
What's the Queen up to now?
Hang on a minute!
The Queen sent her last message
from the network station, right?
That's why her message only
aired on one channel on TV...
Yeah...
Then... wouldn't this be...
Impossible?!
I have organized an event
specifically for Right owners.
To launch this special event,
we will be conducting Tasuketsu
within Tokyo's 23 wards tonight.
Tasuketsu?!
No way!
It's the Emperor!
It's possible!
The Emperor's body was missing...
With the power of resurrection... Damn it!
Depending on the question, we could all die!
I thought the Emperor couldn't
submit questions himself!
The Queen resurrected him!
She must be standing beside
him providing questions!
Omi! No matter what happens,
you gotta stay alive!
Gotcha!
It's time. We will now
begin tallying the majority.
I reject!
You're a male with the blood type RH-O
who has lived in Niimi City, Okayama Prefecture.
What the hell is this?
He's targeting a specific person?
The jig is up...
We've passed midnight.
Tasuketsu: Fate of the Majority
We will now begin our new
event, the Killer Game.
The aim is to kill as many
Right owners as possible within Tokyo
between now and the end of the game.
Winners will be those within the top 10%.
As of midnight tomorrow,
those outside the 23 wards
and losers of the game
will be executed as needed.
Good luck to all participants.
Now for...
Prime Right of Recovery.
All Right owners in Tokyo have died
and I've recovered their Rights.
Who knew working with the Queen
would make Tasuketsu possible...
Not that my powers will always
be available, as busy as I am.
Lady Kisaragi,
we've surely exterminated the current
Emperor's entire group with this blow.
Oh boy...
I wasn't expecting this.
They may have all died with that one...
Y-You guys...
How are you all safe?!
I... have no clue...
We were definitely supposed
to die with that question.
Lucky us...
Protect
It was that!
The envelope with the command!
I opened it while commanding in my head
to protect all of us from Tasuketsu.
Nice move, Gobo!
Envelopes with commands?
Oh yeah... It's basically our key to
enforce the Prime Right of Obedience.
Its owner was a boy named
Teppei Yoshii, but he died.
He set a trick to retain ownership
of the Right even after his death,
and passed it on to his friend, Ren Iruga.
Ren Iruga?
We'll tell you all the deets later.
Just think of it as a secret
weapon we got from Iruga.
The only two commands we have left
are "destroy" and "love".
Either way, we've gotta thank
Gobo for his quick thinking.
Are all these people dead, for real?!
The Emperor's really back, isn't he?
He was able to conduct Tasuketsu,
so I'm assuming all the lost Rights
have been restored, too.
After all that Sane risked to defeat him...
How could he be back?!
It won't be long before the Emperor
figures out we're still alive
after realizing he
couldn't recover our Rights.
That's when the Killer Game
will come into play.
He could also conduct another round
of Tasuketsu and take tally again.
We escaped the last round by chance.
There's no way we survive another round.
There's no point in our plan
to lure out the Queen now.
We're totally out of options.
Either way, our focus for now has to be
to gather information and find safe grounds.
Let's do what we can.
If he really did plant something in Knight...
If Iruga's information turns out to be true...
We have to wait for Knight's next move!
Hey, hag...
Can I ask a favor?
Well this is a surprise.
What is it?
I want you to let me see Mom and Lili!
Just one time!
After that, I'll work even harder!
Fine.
However...
You'll have to make do with just Lili.
What about my mom?!
Your mother is a hostage,
and it'll stay that way.
If you disobey me,
I'll kill her in a heartbeat.
Okay...
I'm glad you're such a good boy.
But please...
Can we go just you and me?!
I... don't like that guy...
Fine.
Wait outside.
By yourself?
He won't act out as long as I mention
his mother is being held hostage.
Man! I'm bored.
Can I go to the bathroom?
Why of course.
I didn't know this building was here!
Lili is in here.
Lili!
Thank God...
You really are safe!
Are you satisfied now?
Yeah...
Then let's head back.
Um... Now that I saw her and all...
Thank you!
The magic words are "Thank you"
and "Cock-A-Doodle-Doo."
They become a spell to freeze
time of anything you touch.
I did it!
Now I just have to...
To the roof!
Prime Right of Recovery.
Recover all knives within
a two-kilometer radius.
Prime Right of Imitation!
All knives!
Imitate the same movement!
Destruction Right!
Right of Flight!
Cock-A-Doodle-Doo!
What's up, Pres?
That's the signal...
Prime Right of Induction.
Flying at supersonic speed
would have been too hard on them...
Welcome, Kato siblings.
I'm glad you came.
Knight tricked me?!
It's as though time slipped away...
This can only be... The Suspension Right...
Tojuro Yagihashi!
I've gained a grasp of the overall picture.
Thank you, Knight-kun.
Let's recap.
At the top is the Queen, and at a similar
level are the Emperor and Seraphiel.
Just below that are the Three Powers,
then Touya Mutsuki...
Ren Iruga and Yohei Fukami's
positions are unknown.
And Hirayama and Hikaru Ebina
are on your side,
which means they're our comrades, as well.
As we thought, the Queen has the power
to both grant and take away Rights.
And she even has the Resurrection Right.
No wonder why that guy with the
Immobilization Right was strong...
I wonder if they can come here somehow...
Above all, our aim is the Queen.
We've gotta take down that
resurrection factory of doom.
As of right now, besides us and
whoever applied to that last question...
The entire population of Tokyo should be dead.
In the name of the Killer Game, the Emperor
ordered all people to head to Tokyo.
He's planning to use survivors as pawns
to find and annihilate us.
He mentioned that people outside of Tokyo
would be executed starting tomorrow.
It was to prevent us from
escaping outside of Tokyo.
H-Hey, Yagihashi?
You think Lili's okay?
She might be asleep under
the influence of some kind of Right.
I've frozen her in time for now.
She'll be safe as long as she's frozen.
Let's release the Suspension Right
once we figure out a solution.
Thanks!
The first task is to figure out our defenses.
Let's all head to the other room.
I bet you're tired!
We've got a massage chair, you know!
It's the best, you should try it!
It's so relaxing!
Yagihashi... Sudo...
What are you guys plotting?!
Kisaragi-san, can you tell me what happened?
He got me...
He used Knight as a medium to
attack me with the Suspension Right!
Now, Knight and Lili are both gone.
So that request of his was a trap then.
I'm sure Tojuro planted an idea
in his head and manipulated him!
I thought he'd figure out my
end goal and join me, but...
I never should have given him
the Suspension Right!
We should be able to defend ourselves
just fine with all the Rights in our hands.
We were caught off guard, Emperor!
Maybe cooperating in conducting
Tasuketsu isn't as easy as I thought?
Was she exposed to some unusual sacrifice?
Oh well.
Anyways, seeing as nature's blessings
will drown out our voices to the outside,
why not call each other by our usual names?
Big sis.
Haruto.
Covertness